Massage Relaxation
Beauty - Health - Diet
Nope... Nuh-uh...
I heard you mumbling in here. You okay?
Yeah. It's just that they
haven't lost much weight...
Do you think I should- whoa!
What's with the outfit?!
I bought some new gear,
so I wanted to show it off!
Oh, for yoga?
You've been way into it lately.
A friend of mine opened up a new studio.
Hot Yoga Studio
Drop by sometime and give it a try!
You can rent the place out!
Plus-Sized Elf
Closed for Private Event
Otherworldly Beings and Super Spicy Poses
Hi, ladies. It's nice to see you again.
Why'd ya dwag us here?
Now, now... He says it'll help us lose weight.
Where's the harm?
Shut your twap!
I don't give a wat's ass, so wemme go!
It's uncomfortably warm in this building...
I'm gonna turn into merrow jerky!
You told us to meet you here
for a workout session,
but what exactly are we doing?
Are we boxing again?
Not this time.
Then... are we dancing?
Wait, is this a torture chamber?!
No, of course not!
Wow, for real?
These losers must live under a rock!
Sounds like you know what we're doing, Oga.
In that case, do you mind...?
Sure, I'll give 'em the rundown.
I appreciate it.
Go ahead and take this.
What is it?
So ya finawwy caved, eh, human?
No, it's not a bribe!
It's clothes and towels!
There are lockers in the back,
so feel free to use them.
Alright, follow me!
'Kay, we're ready!
Sorry for the wait.
Wh-wh-why are you naked?!
Whaddya mean?
'Cause it's a sauna. Duh.
Time to bare our souls, amirite?
In my case, it's bare-bones!
I wonder where the ice baths are...
A friendly word of advice:
put a towel down before you sit.
That is, if you don't want to embarrass yourself
like that flab-biscuit of an elf over there.
Hey! You did exactly the same thing!
Ladies! Put your clothes back on!
Don't touch me, you potato-headed pissant!
You're the one who started it,
Butt-cheeks McGee!
Calm down, you two!
This is quite the pickle...
What's the matter, Mr. Human?
Just forget about them and crank up the heat.
It's NOT a sauna!
Now PLEASE get dressed!
"Hot yoga"?
Oh! I read about yoga in
a dieting book once.
It's a type of fitness training that emphasizes
physical posture and breathing techniques.
Correct.
When practiced in a high-heat,
high-humidity environment,
it's referred to as "hot yoga."
That's completely differ'nt than
what the ogre told us!
Saunas are hot and humid,
so it's close enough, right?
In a manner of speaking...
Well, I'm down for anything, but...
will it help us lose weight?
Absolutely!
It can also reduce inflammation,
resulting in a slimmer face.
A slim face...
Yoga makes it easier to lose weight
by boosting your metabolism.
It's a popular form of exercise.
Oooh...
Now, everyone stand on top of your yoga mats.
All you have to do is imitate my poses.
That's amazing!
But what if we can't?
My body isn't very flexible...
Not a problem!
We'll start with some poses that are
suitable for everyone, even beginners.
Alright then, let's get started!
I want each of you to sit
cross-legged on your mat.
'Kay!
Does that count as cross-legged?
Well, she IS sitting.
A dog can only do so much.
I'm not a dog.
This is a foundational yoga pose
called "Sukhasana."
It's important to avoid canting
your pelvis forward or backward.
A pelvic tilt can cause
your stomach to stick out.
What?!
That's perfect, Kuroeda!
Try to copy the way she's keeping
her hips flat against the floor.
The hell are you smirking at?!
Don't get bent out of shape!
Focus on your posture and
your breathing, and relax...
Relax your shoulders...
Take controlled breaths...
This pose is often used
during meditation, too.
I'm all sweaty and we aren't even moving...
I'm gonna shrivel up and die!
Don't forget to drink plenty of water.
Got it!
Good job!
Let's move on to some poses that
target specific areas of the body!
This one's pretty tough...
"Supine Spinal Twist" is a pose
that improves digestion
and can also boost your metabolism.
I'm shaking...
I'm sweating up a storm...
"Chair Pose" is effective for tightening,
sculpting, and strengthening the lower body.
Raising your arms into "Crescent Moon Pose"
stretches your shoulders and back.
It bends your spine into
the shape of a crescent moon...
It does wonders for my stiff shoulders!
"Downward-Facing Dog" is beneficial for
toning your arms, calves, and hamstrings.
My arms are wobblin' like jelly!
By training your core muscles,
"Tree Pose" can be an effective way to
reduce inflammation and sensitivity to cold.
It utilizes your whole body!
I think I'd wike it even better if
it was "Money Twee Pose"...
The gang's all here...
What are they up to in there?
What's that pose called?
"Lion Pose."
Lion...?
Are you sure it's not called "Piggy Pose"?
Huh? Aw, do I look like a cute little piggy?
Oink-hee-hee!
I don't think it was a compliment...
Can you tell me if I'm doing this right?
Mr. Human, could you take a look
at my pose next?
Mine, too!
Th-they're showing off a bunch of sexy poses
in front of the human...
Whoa, one at a time!
Y'know, I can't help but notice that
you're all soaked in sweat.
I didn't wear you out, did I?
S-soaked?!
W-wear them out?!
M-my poor, innocent psyche!
Wow, you ladies really catch on quick!
You're making fantastic progress!
You think so?
Aw, shucks!
Oh man... It's hard to stay balanced...
That's because you're a little stiff.
Go slowly, but try not to overexert yourself.
Yeah, I hear you.
Hmmmmm?
Just hang in there!
You'll get it eventually!
SMACK!
What the hell was that for?!
Don't pretend like you
weren't picking a fight!
I'll punt your big balloon belly
into outer space!
In that case, I'll make sure you leave with your
enormous ass even more swollen than usual!
Hey, you're going to distract everyone!
Take it easy!
They're at each other's throats again?
Awfully tempermental, aren't they?
Atta girl, giving it your best shot!
'Cause I want more pwesents
fwom kids at the park.
Whaddya call that pose?
That's "Happy Baby Pose."
Happy baby...?!
Oh my goodness gracious!
Do you wanna be a wittle baby?
Then I'll gladly be your mommy!
Wet me go! I can't bweathe!
You should never force your way
into a child's personal space.
She's wight!
The cycwops has way better
motherwy instincts than you!
Kids call 'em like they see 'em.
Excuse me?
Well, anyone with eyes can see
that MY people are the superior species.
If it's a fight you want,
it's a fight you'll get.
The winner is her REAL mother!
Sure, fine by me.
We never declared a winner
after our boxing match the other day.
Don't I get a say in this?!
Only because we ran out of time.
Technically speaking, I won.
You got vision problems or something?
No matter how you slice it, I won.
Not them too...!
W-wait a minute!
What the heck?!
Stop! Cut it out, you two!
All I wanted was for us to do yoga
and have fun in a healthy way...
How did it turn into this?
Hold on...
It looks like Honeda's completely
unbothered by the situation...
And her form...
It's like she's a yoga master!
I won't back down!
W-watch out!
She dodged it!
Like a TRUE yoga master!
I heard the Dragon Slenderer's voice just now...
Is he experimenting with a new technique?
She's speaking inside my mind...?
Dragon Slenderer...
I would like to learn this
new technique of yours as well.
Teach me and I shall reward you with riches.
Wiches, you say?!
Yo, dragon. This is a yoga studio.
You gotta take those off first.
I see.
Why are you getting undressed?!
I meant your shoes, not your pants!
Horns and a tail...
Is she a dragon?!
And a pudgy one at that!
Shh! That's very rude!
Come now, human. The technique.
Human? Wait, is he...?
Are you okay?
H-he's out like a light!
No, look closely!
That's... "Corpse Pose"!